

Date of Birth: 29/01/1990 | 052-6740710 | matan3sh@gmail.com **Portfolio: matanshaviro.herokuapp.com | Github: github.com/matan3sh**

About Me

I'm highly motivated team player & fast learner. Looking for a junior position as a developer. I have a passion for programming since I was 14 years old, an analytical mind, productive, creative ability and always pay attention to details.

Skills & Abilities

PROJECTS DEGREE:

- **Departmental Excellence Final Project [Score 97]** Development of a revolutionizing social network app for wandering and lost pets, Based **React Native** using **Firebase** database.
 - Received a social scholarship and selected project at 2019 Engineers Society.
- Developed an e-commerce based **ReactJS** client side using **Redux** and **NodeJS** server side.
- Developed a DApp Solidity, Truffle Framework and Ganache as a virtual blockchain machine using Metamask as Ethereum wallet.

FREELANCE DEVELOPER:

 Developed a Management platform for Yes Planet Projection Room department, based on JAVA, JAVA GUI system (NetBeans), SQL Server Management Studio.

KNOWLEDGE OF:

- Cross-Platform mobile apps development using React Native, Flutter based Dart Language.
- Self-Learning: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript focused on ReactJS, NextJS, VueJS.
- Experience working with **Firebase**, **Mongo** databases.
- Familiar with Programming Languages: C, C++, C#, JAVA, PYTHON and Oracle SQL Developer.
- Assembly, Object-Oriented and Multi-Threaded programming proficient with Design Patterns, Bash Scripting in Linux\Unix operation system.
- Cryptographic mechanisms underlying in **Blockchain** technology, Implementing a smart contract in **Solidity** on the Ethereum Virtual Machine.

Education

- SCE COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING | BEER SHEVA | 2015 2019 | BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING
- TECHNOLOGICAL COLLEGE | BEER SHEVA | 2008-2010 | PRACTICAL ELECTRONIC ENGINEER
- ITZHAK RAGER HIGH SCHOOL | 2003 2008 | COMPUTER SOFTWARE MAJOR

Work Experience

PROJECTION ROOM MANAGER | 2016-2018 | Yes Planet Cinema Beer- Sheva

- Manage a crew of people, Responsibility for all film programs and cinema technical system.
- High frequency communication with IMAX corporation at Canada and South Korea.

Army

TECHNICIAN OF ELECTRONIC WARFARE SYSTEMS | 2010-2013 | Full military service

- Electronic warfare systems technician course.
 - Expertise and experience in RF electronics.
 - Training in designated warfare systems: Elta, Tadiran Systems and Netline.

LANGUAGES:

• Hebrew - mother tongue | English - fluently